Once upon a time, there was a creature named Wynn
C’era una volta, una creatura di nome Wynn.
lost in the deep, where cold currents creep.
Sperduta negli abissi, dove strisciano le correnti gelide.
He had no memories, no sky, no shore.
Non aveva ricordi, né cielo, né riva.
One day
Un giorno
he drifted against a jar tangled in the sand.
si scontrò con un vaso impigliato nella sabbia.
Inside, a swirl of silent eyes
Dentro, un vortice di occhi silenziosi
each holding a world, a life, a sky.
ognuno custodiva un mondo, una vita, un cielo.
When Wynn touched the glass
Quando Wynn sfiorò il vetro
visions poured through.
visioni si riversarono in lui.
Fields in bloom
Campi in fiore
skies of blue
cieli d’azzurro
laughter
risa
running
corse
falling rain.
pioggia che cade.
All the things he had never known
Tutte le cose che non aveva mai conosciuto
and all the colors he had never seen.
e tutti i colori che non aveva mai visto.
Carrying the jar through the endless blue
Portando con sé il vaso attraverso l’infinito blu
Wynn realized
Wynn comprese
he wasn't just seeing others’ memories
che non stava solo guardando ricordi altrui
he was gathering dreams for his own.
ma raccoglieva sogni per sé.
And when he placed the jar atop a coral tower
E quando posò il vaso in cima a una torre di corallo
the memories drifted into the sea
i ricordi si dispersero nel mare
painting the darkness with light
dipingendo l’oscurità di luce
with color, with song.
di colore, di canto.
Wind smiled for the first time.
Wynn sorrise,  per la prima volta.
He wasn't lost anymore.
Non era più perduto.
He had made a world of his own.
Veva creato un mondo tutto suo.